Theresa Wolfson Papers 5216
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IV. LITERARY MANUSCRIPTS, 1925-1960
  - Sub-Series A. Drafts of books, articles, etc.
    - Fiscal Policy (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Fringe Benefits (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Garment Industry (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Gompers, Samuel (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - How Does Modern Education Fail Women (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Industrial Conflict (Box 26, Folder 8-9)
    - Industrial Unionism (Box 27, Folder 1-5)
    - Jewish Women in the American Labor Market (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Labor and Inflation (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Labor-Management Participation (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
    - Labor Philosophy (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Labor's Coming of Age (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Love is Not Enough (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - National Recovery Administration (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Needle Trades Union and the NRA (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - New Educational Frontier (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Organized Labor and Political Action (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
    - Organized Labor and the Community (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Peace and Bread (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Prejudice (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Price and Real Wage Data (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Recent Social Climate (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Rifton Strike (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Search for Security (Box 28, Folder 12-14)
    - Socialism in the World Today (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Some Facts About Women Today (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Soviet Unemployed Insurance (Box 29, Folder 2-8)
    - Stabilization in the Men's and Women's Garment Industry (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - State of the Unions (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Tax Concern of the American Labor Movement (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Trade Union Education League (Box 29, Folder 12-13)
    - Trade Union Policy and Government Regulations (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Trends in the American Labor Movement (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Two Women Look at the Labor Movement (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Unemployment (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Unemployment Insurance (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
    - Union Policy and Technological Change (Box 30, Folder 4-5)
    - Wages (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Wages and Woozles (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - War Time Labour Development in Australia (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Why We Write This Pamphlet (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Women (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Women - Position in Society (Box 30, Folder 11-12)
    - Worker on the Delaware-Hudson Canal (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Yearbook (articles written for Collier's Yearbook) (Box 30, Folder 14-16)
    - Yearbook (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
    - Articles, 1925-1952 (Box 31, Folder 3-10)
    - Sub-Series 1. Project - Inverviewing labor leaders for "Philosophy of Labor.", 1947-1948
      Contains notes on interviews and mss. Drafts.
      - Outline of project (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Introduction (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Drafts of chapters (Box 32, Folder 3-4)
      - Sub-Series a. Interview summaries and notes
        - Alameda County (Calif.) Central Labor Council (Robert Ash) (Box 32, Folder 5)
        - Automobile Workers (Box 32, Folder 6)
        - Clothing Workers, Amalgamated (Box 32, Folder 7)
        - CIO, Chicago (Box 32, Folder 8)
        - CIO, Los Angeles (Box 32, Folder 9)
        - CIO, San Francisco (Box 32, Folder 10)
        - Garment Workers (Box 32, Folder 11)
        - Longshoremen's Union, International (Box 32, Folder 12)
        - Machinists, International Association of (Box 32, Folder 13)
        - Meat Cutters, Amalgamated (Box 32, Folder 14)
        - Michigan Workers Education Service (Box 32, Folder 15)
        - Oil Workers Internationl Union (Box 32, Folder 16)
        - Packinghouse Workers of America (Box 32, Folder 17)
        - Printers Union (Box 32, Folder 18)
        - Printing Trades (Box 32, Folder 19)
        - Retail Clerks (Calif.) (Box 32, Folder 20)
        - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees (Box 32, Folder 21)
        - Rubber Workers International Union (Box 32, Folder 22)
        - San Francisco Bay District, Building Service (Box 32, Folder 23)
        - San Francisco Labor Council (Box 32, Folder 24)
        - San Francisco Labor Research Bureau (Box 32, Folder 25)
        - San Francisco State Federation of Labor (Box 32, Folder 26)
        - Steel Workers Union, United (Box 32, Folder 27-29)
        - Teamsters, International Brotherhood of (Box 32, Folder 30)
        - Textile Workers Union of America (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series B. Reviews of books and articles
    Arranged by name of author.
    - Barbash, Jack (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Bestor, Arthur (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Blake (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Braun, Kurt (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Brooks, Robert (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Corey, Lewis (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Dunn, Robert W. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Epstein, Abraham (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Finke, Mary B. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Folksocialism (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Gloerfelt-Tarp, Kirsten (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Gordon, Manya (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Hutchison, Keith (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Knowles, William (Box 33, Folder 14-15)
    - Liveright, A.A. (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Lowin, Louis (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Pearlman, S. (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Pollack, Katherine H. (Box 33, Folder 19-20)
    - Tilove, Robert (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Watson, Goodwin (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous unidentified manuscripts (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Series V. SUBJECT FILES
  All Frances Wright materials in boxes 34-43 were transferred to Krock Library Rare and Manuscripts as collection Archives 6934. The transferred materials include: Research materials and manuscripts collected by Wolfson for the book Frances Wright, Free Inquirer, published in 1939, which Wolfson co-authored with A.J.G. (Alice Gray) Perkins. Include correspondence (1909-1967) chiefly between Wolfson and Perkins, researchers, and various research institutions seeking biographical, genealogical and publication data on Frances Wright; drafts (mss. typewritten) of the book chapters, index, and bibliography; biographical data on Wright consisting of mss. notes; excerpts and drafts. The excerpts (mss.) were copied chiefly by Perkins from letters of Wright and from the newspapers Nnew Harmony Gazette (1825- 1828) and Free Inquirer (1828-1831). Wright's correspondents include Richard Wright, Mrs. Craig Millar, Charles Wilkes, James Milne, the Marquis de Lafayette, William Roscoe, B. Flower, Jeremy Bentham, Robert Dale Owen, Camilla Wright, Phiquepal D'Arusmont, and Marie Louise Duclos Fretageot. Also excerpts from the poetry of Wright, Wright's Commonplace Book, Owen's diary, and the Book of Nashoba kept by James Richardson and Sylvie D'Arusmont's diary (child of Wright and Phiquepal D'Arusmont). Includes the original ms. of Frances Wright's Last Will and Testament (1852); photocopies of Wright's correspondence with Robert Dale Owen and the Marquis de Lafayette; mss. maps of Nashoba Territory in West Tennessee; printed deeds of the lands of Nashoba (1827); ms. address by Wright (1827) on the nature and object of the institution at Nashoba and its founding principles; mss. deeds and agreements (1746-1834). Also original mss. speeches and lectures of Wright: The Six Ephochs of Human History (history of human civilization: its beginning in India, Egypt, Greece, and Rome and its later phases in medieval and modern Europe); View of the Political Horizon (1838); Free Public Speech: the Clarion of Popular Liberty (1838); an account of Wright's ideal America (1839); a lecture on religion (n.d.); a lecture (no title) delivered at the Masonic Hall in New York (1839); 4 other untitled lectures; and 16 volumes of lectures. Also, the published writings of Wright, photocopies of lithographs, and clippings.
  - Sub-Series A. Fanny Wright
    - All Fanny Wright material transferred to Cornell's Rare and Manuscript Collections (Box 34-43)
      See RMC Collection no.6934: Files and manuscripts regarding Frances (Fanny) D'Arusmont Wright, 1746-1967.
  - Sub-Series B. Files on workers' education, 1930-1961
    Documents Wolfson's activities in the area of continuing education for workers. Include minutes, form letters, routine correspondence, course outlines, publications, reports, papers, agenda, reprints, programs, news releases, syllabi, and manuscript notes on the following schools and organizations involved in workers' education: Affiliated Schools for Workers (1931-1938); American Federation of Labor Committee on Education (n.d.); American Labor Education Service (ALES) (formerly the Affiliated Schools for Workers (1941-1961); Barnard Summer School (1925-1930); Brookwood Labor College (1921-1931); Bryn Mawr Summer School (1924-1938); Civic Club Committee on Labor Education (1921); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Education Department (1920-1954); International Labor Office (1958-1959); National League Summer School (1925, 1927), Southern Summer School (1933-1936); Summer School for Office Workers (1927-1950); and Workers Defense League (1931, 1937, 1959).
    - Affiliated Schools for Workers (Box 44, Folder 1-5)
    - AFL Committee on Education (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - American Labor Education Service (ALES) - Atomic Energy (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - ALES - Clippings (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - ALES - Colorado State (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - ALES - CIO Seminar (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - ALES - Committee on International Exchange (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - ALES - Correspondence, 1943-1962 (Box 45, Folder 6-10)
    - ALES - Discrimination (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - ALES - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - ALES - International Project (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - ALES - International Relations Seminar (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - ALES - Minutes, 1943-1962 (Box 46, Folder 1-6)
    - ALES - Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - ALES - Miscellaneous Programs (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - ALES - New Jersey Minorities Project (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - ALES - Northwest Farmers (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - ALES - Ohio Conference (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - ALES - Reports (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - ALES - St. Louis (Box 47, Folder 3-4)
    - ALES - Statement of Program and Policy (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - ALES - United Nations (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - ALES - Washington's Birthday Conference (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - ALES - White Collar Workshops (Box 48, Folder 2-11)
    - ALES - World Affairs (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - ALES - Publications (Box 49, Folder 1-5)
    - ALES - Photographs (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Barnard Summer School (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Brookwood Labor College (Box 50, Folder 2-5)
    - Bryn Mawr Summer School (Box 50, Folder 6-12)
    - Bryn Mawr Summer School (Box 51, Folder 1-7)
    - Civic Club Committee on Labor Education (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, Education Department (Box 52, Folder 1-5)
    - International Labor Office, Workers Education (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Labor Education (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - National League Summer School (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Southern Summer School (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Summer Institute for Office Workers (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Sumer School for Office Workers (Box 53, Folder 3-8)
    - Trade Union (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Vocational Education (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - White Collar Workers (Box 54, Folder 3-6)
    - Woman's Auxiliary (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Workers Defense League (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Workers Education Conference - Sweden (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Workers Education - General (Box 54, Folder 10-15)
    - Workers Education Bureau (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Workers Party (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series C. Japanese Sabbatic
    - Japanese Sabbatic, 1962-1963 (Box 55-56, Folder All)
      Includes notes, publications, clippings collected during Professor Wolfson's sabbatical leave in Japan
  - Sub-Series D. Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1920-1970
    Arranged alphabetically. Consists of materials collected by Wolfson on a variety of subjects, including civil liberties, research in industrial relations, international labor, labor legislation, unemployment, teachers, white collar workers, and women. Includes publications, form letters, agenda, news releases, correspondence, articles, and manuscript notes collected by Wolfson on the following subjects: American Civil Liberties Union (1941-1969); Columbia University, Seminar on Labor (1953-1967); Industrial Relations Research Association (1951-1962); international labor (1930-1969) in Africa, Australia, Austria, Canada, France, Germany, Great Britain, India, Israel, Italy, Japan, Latin America, New Zealand, Scandinavia, United States, and USSR; Wolfson's sabbatical leave in Japan (1962-1963); National Labor Relations Act (1920-1936); National Labor Relations Board (1936-1937); National Industrial Recovery Act (1933-1934); New York State Temporary Commission Against Discrimination (1944-1957); Social Security (1935-1955); Teachers Union (1938-1968); unemployment (1928-1933); unemployment insurance (1932-1954); unemployment remedies (1929-1933); wages (1928-1941); War Labor Board (1937-1955); white collar workers (1958); and women (1880-1961). Materials on women are divided into the following categories: bibliographies, discrimination, education, general, hours of work, in defense, Knights of Labor, legislation, organizing, personal objectives, trade unions, unemployment, wages, war workers, workers, YWCA (Young Women's Christian Association), Centennial Congress, International League, and women's rights.
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1941-1969 (Box 57, Folder 1-5)
    - American Humanitarian Labor Alliance, 1920 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - American Nurses Association, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Apprenticeship - NY Industries, 1931 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Association for Evolutionary Economics, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Automation, 1955-1956 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Automobile Workers, 1942-1950 (Box 57, Folder 11-12)
    - California, Univ. of, Extension Division, 1946-1948 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Chamberlain, Neil, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Check-off, 1937-1939 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Child Labor, 1926-1929 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Child Study Association, 1936-1955 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Childs, Frances, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Choice, 1964-1970 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Columbia University Seminar on Labor, 1953-1967 (Box 58, Folder 8-9)
    - Columbia University Seminar on Labor, 1953-1967 (Box 59-61, Folder All)
    - Committee on Economic Security, 1935 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Community Education (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Commons, John R., 1935-1945 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - CIO Community Services Committee, 1949-1951 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Economics, Univ. of Chicago, 1946-1947 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Full Employment (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Gomberg, William (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Health, 1955-1963 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Industrial Relations Research Association, 1952-1955 (Box 62, Folder 9-11)
    - Industrial Relations Research Association, 1951-1962 (Box 63, Folder 1-4)
    - Immigration (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - International Industrial Relations institute, 1929-1934 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - International Labor - Africa, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - International Labor - Australia, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - International Labor - Austria (Box 63, Folder 9)
      no date
    - International Labor - Canada (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - International Labor - France (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - International Labor - Germany, 1930-1955 (Box 63, Folder 12-15)
    - International Labor - Gt. Britain (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - International Labor - India, 1956-1957 (Box 64, Folder 2-3)
    - International Labor - Israel, 1952-1956 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - International Labor - Italy, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - International Labor - Japan, 1933-1956 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - International Labor - Latin Americas (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - International Labor - Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - International Labor - Miscellaneous (Box 65, Folder 1-4)
    - International Labor - New Zealand (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - International Labor - Scandinavian Countries (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - International Labor - Sweden, 1958 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - International Labor - U.S. (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - International Labor - USSR, 1935-1969 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Labor Group, 1944-1946 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Labor Legislation (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Labor-Management Relations, 1948-1951 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Labor movement - Pacific Coast, 1938 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Ladies Garment Workers, 1934 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Laidler, Harry W., 1965-1968 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - League for Industrial Democracy, 1953-1954 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Longshoremen, 1947-1948 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Lord Snell (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Metropolitan Economic Association (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Minimum Wage, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Motion Picture, Extras, 1935-1940 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - National Child Labor Committee, 1919-1920 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - National Consumer's League, 1957-1958 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - National Industrial Recovery Act, 1933-1935 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - National Labor Relations Act, 1920-1936 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - National Labor Relations Board, 1936-1937 (Box 66, Folder 8-10)
    - National Recovery Act, 1933-1934 (Box 66, Folder 11-13)
    - National War Labor Board, 1945 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - NYC Labor Relations Code, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - NYS Commission Against Discrimination, 1944-1957 (Box 67, Folder 2-5)
    - Open Shop, 1942 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Ornati, Oscar A., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Perlman, Selig, 1949 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Personnel Club of New York, 1952 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - President's Emergency Committee for Employment, 1931-1938 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Public Education, 1951 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - "Quadrangle", 1939-1940 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Social Security, 1935-1955 (Box 68, Folder 8-10)
    - Social Service, 1937-1939 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Southern Tenant Farmers Union, 1939 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Strikes, 1950 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Taft-Hartley, 1953-1961 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Tax Research Institute of America, 1938 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Teachers - General, 1940-1952 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Teachers Guild, 1950 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Teachers Union, 1938-1968 (Box 69, Folder 5-7)
    - Teaching, 1958-1961 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1947 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Textile Workers Union, 1949 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Unemployment, 1928-1933 (Box 69, Folder 11-13)
    - Unemployment Insurance, 1932-1954 (Box 70, Folder 1-3)
    - Unemployment Insurance - Wisconsin, 1935-1936 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Unemployment Remedies, 1929-1933 (Box 70, Folder 5-6)
    - Union Growth, 1954 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - United Labor Education Committee, 1920 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - United Nations, 1950-1953 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Wage Patterns, 1947-1948 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Wage Stabilization Board, 1951 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Wages, 1928-1941 (Box 71, Folder 2-3)
    - War Labor Board, 1937-1955 (Box 71, Folder 4-7)
    - War Resisters League, 1938 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Welfare Pensions, 1947-1954 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - White Collar Workers, 1958 (Box 72, Folder 1-3)
    - World Labor Organizations (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Women - Bibliographies (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Women - Discrimination, 1949-1951 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Women - Education (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Women - General, 1920-1930 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Women - Hours of Work, 1929 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Women - In Defense, 1941-1943 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Women - Knights of Labor, 1880-1890 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Women - Legislation, 1937-1948 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Women - Organizing, 1927 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Women - Personal Objectives, 1958 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Women - Trade Unions, 1926 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Women - Unemployment (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Women - Wages, 1933 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Women - War Workers, 1943-1944 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Women Workers, 1924-1961 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Women Workers, Foreign (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Women - YWCA, 1937-1945 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Women - YWCA, Questionnaire, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Women's Centennial Congress, 1940 (Box 73, Folder 12-13)
    - Women's international league, 1937 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Women's Rights, 1929-1946 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Young People's Socialist League, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 16)
- Series VI. Pamphlets
  - Sub-Series Pamphlets and Articles by Wolfson
    - A- America's Home Grown Exiles (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - C- CIO vs. AFL, Curse on Cotton (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - D- Democratic Pattern & Minority Groups (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - E- Education During a Strike (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - H- Health Service for Garment Workers (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - I- Investigation into Seating and Posture in the Garment Trades (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - J- Jews in Labor and Industry (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - L- Labor and the NRA, Labor's Coming of Age (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - N- New Educational Frontier (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - O- Overcoming Prejudice (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - P- People Who Go To Beets, Posture and Fatigue (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - R- Role of the ILGWU in Stabilizing the Women's Garment Industry (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - S- Schools the Miners Keep, Social Control of Industrial Conflict (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - T- Trade Union Activities of Women, Trade Union Promises (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - U- Union Finances and Elections (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - W- White Collar Worker Asks Questions, White Collar Workers - Yellow, White Collars are Wilting, Women's Auxiliary to Trade Unions and Workers Education (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Y- Youth and Peace (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Reviews by Theresa Wolfson (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Pamphlets - Signed by Authors (Box 74)
    - A-B, 1945-1966 (Box 74, Folder 19)
      - Item 1: Adler, John - The Underdeveloped Areas: Their Industrialization, 1949; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 19)
        Format: Pamphlet.
      - Item 2: Almond, Gabriel H. - The Political Attitudes of Wealth, 1945; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 19)
      - Item 3: Baker, Elizabeth F. - The Printing Foreman-Union Man: A Historical Sketch, 1951; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 19)
      - Item 4: Benewitz, Maurice C. - The 1958 Temporary Unemployment Compensation Act, Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 19)
      - Item 5: Bloch, Herman D. - Craft Unions and the Negro in Historical Perspective, 1958; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 19)
      - Item 6: Bloch, Herman D. Economic Effects of Discrimination in Employment, 1966; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 19)
      - Item 7: Bloch, Herman D. The New York Negro's Reaction to Tension, 1827-1865, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - C, 1941-1956 (Box 74, Folder 20)
      - Item 1: Cary, Otis - Uchimura, Neesima and Amherst-Recently Discovered Correspondence, 1956; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 20)
      - Item 2: Chernick, Jack - A Guide to the Guaranteed Wage, 1955; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 20)
      - Item 3: Clarkson, jesse Dunsmore - Escape to the Present, 1941; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - D, 1928-1949 (Box 74, Folder 21)
      - Item 1: Dalencour, Francois - Alexandre Petiondevant l'Humanite, 1928; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 21)
      - Item 2: Dunne, George H. - Religion and American Democracy, 1949; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - F, 1961-1967 (Box 74, Folder 22)
      - Item 1: Field, A.R. - Strategic Development in Sinkiang, 1961; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 22)
      - Item 2: Finkelstein, Michael O. - The Application of an Entropy Theory of Concentration to the Clayton Act, 1967; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 22)
      - Item 3: Fried, Hans Ernest - The Frontiers of the Future, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 22)